{
    "status": "success",
    "data": [
      {
        "question": "Which type of tax is taken directly out of your paycheck??",
        "answer": "Your intended date of graduation.",
        "arr": [
          "What kind of grades you earn.",
          "Whether or not you pay your bills on time (your credit history).",
          "Your intended date of graduation.",
          "All of the above"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is a risk to consider when investing?",
        "answer": "Inflation",
        "arr": [
          "You could lose all of your money",
          "Inflation",
          "Your money is not liquid",
          "All of the above"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "In terms of size what position does the Indian economy occupy in the world?",
        "answer": "12th",
        "arr": ["10th", "12th", "7th", "9th "]
      },
      {
        "question": "Which industry provides the largest employment in India?",
        "answer": "Textiles",
        "arr": ["Orenge", "Textiles", "Iron and steel", "Jute"]
      },
      {
        "question": "The Finance Minister Nirmala Sitharaman has launched which app?",
        "answer": "Union Budget Mobile App",
        "arr": [
          "Pay Commission Mobile App",
          "National Budget App",
          "Union Budget Mobile App",
          "Budget App"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "The State Bank of India allocated how much amount towards the fight against Covid 19?",
        "answer": "Rs.71 cr",
        "arr": ["Rs.70 cr", "Rs.92 cr", "Rs.71 cr", "\tRs.60 cr"]
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following organisation has introduced the flagship initiative Liberalised MSME AEO Package scheme?",
        "answer": "CBIC",
        "arr": ["CBIC", "ONGC", "Niti Aayog", "Ministry of Planning"]
      },
      {
        "question": "Government aims to gradually increase the public health expenditure to what percent of Gross Domestic Product by 2025?",
        "answer": 0.025,
        "arr": [0.015, 0.035, 0.045, 0.025]
      },
      {
        "question": "Government aims to gradually increase the public health expenditure to what percent of Gross Domestic Product by 2025?",
        "answer": 0.025,
        "arr": [0.015, 0.035, 0.045, 0.025]
      },
      {
        "question": "Who has been appointed as the 1st chairman of the International Financial Services Centre Authority for a 3 years term?",
        "answer": "Injeti Srinivas",
        "arr": [
          "Injeti Srinivas",
          "Sumanta Chaudhury",
          "Anant Narayan Nanda",
          "Arun Goel"
        ]
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is the current US president",
        "answer": "Biden",
        "arr": ["Obama", "Bush", "Biden", "Trumph"]
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of thw following is a Tech Stack",
        "answer": "MERN",
        "arr": ["MEAN", "MERN", "MYIO", "None of the above"]
      },
      {
        "question": "PM of india",
        "answer": "Narendra modi",
        "arr": ["Narendra Modi", "Manmohan Singh", "Ram Nath Kovind", "Yogi Aditya Nath"]
      }
    ]
  }